#大家好 現在我們那個豬欄啊 圍了一下
Hi everyone! Now the pigsty, I've just fenced it,
#把那個豬放出來
so that the pigs can be released.
#帶大家去看一下
Let me show you.
#就在這裡面啦
They're just inside
#你看 他們跑不出來啦
Look! They can't run away.
#你看這個
Look at this one!
#這個 我還以為它中暑了呢
This one! I thought it had a heat stroke.
#嚇我一大跳
You scare me!
#進去看一下
Let me take a look inside
#這個門沒搞好
The gate is not yet fixed.
#我們就這樣
So we just...
#這樣拴住 它就不會出
you see, they can't get out.
#等下我們要用釘子把它釘兩下
I'll nail it later.
#就行啦
Then it'll be alright.
#你看 這個就是經常放出去散養的那個小豬
Look! That's the pig which was outside the pigsty.
#那麼大條
It's so big.
#放進來現在都搶不到吃的
It can't scramble for the food now when it's inside.
#現在都瘦啦
It's getting skinny now.
#不管它
Never mind
#養 合在一起養好一點 促進一下感情
Keep, when they're kept together, they can build a better relationship.
#小豬
Piggy!
#跑不出去的
You just can't get out.
#跑出去我把你宰了 我跟你說
I'll kill you if you get out. Don't say that I haven't warned you.
#這條豬最不聽話 這條公豬
This is the naughtiest, this male pig.
#就你不聽話
Naughty!
#你看 放出來它們很開心哦
Look! They're all very happy now when they're outside.
#它們都圍著我轉
They all come around me.
#啊 小豬
Ah! Piggy
#他竟然想咬我
It wants to bite me!
#就你最不聽話啦
You're always the naughtiest!
#打你屁股
Spank you!
#等我拿根棍子來打你 看你怕不怕
I' beat you with a rod, and see if you're scared.
#看 這公的
Look! This male pig,
#很不聽話的
is really naughty!
#是不是 想咬我剛才
Aren't you? You just wanted to bite me!
#想咬我了哈
You wanna bite me?
#叫你不聽話
Naughty!
#過年的時候就宰了它
I'll kill it during the Chinese New Year.
#過年的時候就把你吃了
You'll be our Chinese New Year dish.
#這條公的 剛才還想咬我
The male pig, just wanted to bite me.
#我揍它 過年的時候就先把它宰啦
I beat it. It'll be the first pig to be killed during the Chinese New Year.